http://www.schoolspring.com/about/privacypolicy.cfm

Connect with us:
Log In
Username:
Password:
Post a Job
SchoolSpring, Inc. ("SchoolSpring") respects the privacy of its users and their right to restrict the use of their personal information. This Privacy Policy discloses how personal information is collected, protected, used and shared on this site.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using this site. By using this website and its services:
you are agreeing that the terms of our Privacy Policy are acceptable to you;
you do not expect SchoolSpring to take any measures to safeguard personal information other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy; and
you will not do anything to violate the terms of this Privacy Policy yourself.
Any undefined terms used in this Privacy Policy shall refer to areas of this website with the same name. Your use of this site is also subject to the Terms of Use posted on this site. This Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use or any part thereof may be revised from time to time through an updated posting. You should, therefore, check both this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use periodically. Revisions are effective upon posting and your continued use of this site following the posting of such revisions will indicate your acceptance of such revisions. If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, please email us.
Collection of Information
SchoolSpring provides services (the "SchoolSpring Services") that allow (i) job seekers
("Candidates") to search for education job postings, send email messages regarding job postings, store personal and professional information so that SchoolSpring clients can actively recruit potential candidates, and sign up to receive notification of new job postings that match the Candidate's job preferences; and (ii) educational institutions ("Clients") to facilitate and streamline the recruiting and hiring process.
The SchoolSpring Services are available through an Internet site located at the URL address of http://www.schoolspring.com and require personal information to be collected from nearly every user.
There are various levels of access on the site, each of which requires SchoolSpring to gather different kinds of information.
GuestAs a guest, you may take a tour of the website, as well as read information on the different job postings available on the site. This requires neither registration nor log in, and guests are not asked for any personal information.
CandidateAs a Candidate, you may, among other things, create a Candidate Profile, compose a cover letter and send email messages regarding job postings.
In order to provide you with customized, personalized information, you are asked for some specific information about yourself.
SchoolSpring collects personal contact information, including address and phone number; social security number; professional information, including work experience, education experience, and academic performance (including transcripts); and job search preferences of its Candidates.
SchoolSpring uses the information stated above in order to provide resume searching capabilities to its Clients, with the exception of those restricted by the SchoolSpring Candidate and to facilitate and improve the recruiting and hiring process for SchoolSpring Clients and Candidates. You will also need to supply SchoolSpring with a username and a password, which may be updated by you at any time through the site.
ClientAs a Client, you may, among other things, post jobs, search the database of Candidates, receive multiple secure user names and passwords in order to provide various levels of access for districts and schools, and download a User Manual from the site.
In order to provide you with customized service, you are asked for some specific information about yourself and your school or district.
SchoolSpring collects personal contact information, including address and phone number, size of student enrollment and annual job openings. SchoolSpring uses the information stated above to notify Candidates when new jobs are posted that match their job search preferences and to facilitate and improve the recruiting and hiring process for SchoolSpring Clients and Candidates.
You will also need to supply SchoolSpring with a username and a password, which may be updated by you at any time through the site.
Use of Information
SchoolSpring will take appropriate, commercially reasonable steps to keep all personal information securely stored, in order to provide the SchoolSpring Services.
Both Candidate information and Client information is accessible to such Candidate or Client, as the case may be, at any time upon providing a valid username and password on the SchoolSpring.com web site.
SchoolSpring never sells or shares information about its Candidates or Clients to third parties, except in the following circumstances: (a) in response to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, to the extent permitted and as restricted by law; (b) when disclosure is required to maintain the security and integrity of this site, or to protect any Candidate's or Client's security or the security of other persons, consistent with applicable laws; or (c) when disclosure is directed by the Candidate or Client who has inputted the personal information.
When you conduct a transaction through this site, you are providing transaction information to SchoolSpring's third party suppliers (such as transaction processors and financial institutions) who will use the information solely for the purpose of the transaction.
Security
This site uses industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to protect user information and also uses a secure connection to our servers, which are protected by a firewall to prevent unauthorized break-ins. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet is guaranteed completely secure. Given the inherent operation and structure of the Internet, all transmissions are done at your own risk.
Updating Your Information
SchoolSpring retains indefinitely all the information SchoolSpring gathers about you in an effort to make your repeat use with us more efficient, practical, and relevant. Of course, you can correct or update your profile, your applications, your job postings and your other personal information, as the case may be, at any time. Moreover, you can delete your profile from SchoolSpring's online database, remove or close your account(s) at any time, in which event we will remove your profile and other personal information, as the case may be, from the SchoolSpring site. However, all job postings and job applications will be stored indefinitely for later retrieval by the appropriate candidate or client.
Use of Cookies
The use of cookies is common in the Internet industry. Cookies are small text files that a website transfers to your computer's browser. Cookie technology tells the website non-personally identifiable information, but does identify your computer, browser and Internet specifications. This site uses cookie technology to customize your session and retain your log-in information.
You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline all cookies if you prefer. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on the SchoolSpring site.
SchoolSpring uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
IP Addresses
An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider. This site may collect IP addresses, the associated URLs, domain types, the browser type used to access the site, the pages of this site that users viewed during their visit and any search terms entered on the site. Collection of IP addresses is generally for system administration purposes, to monitor the level of activity on the site and for security reasons. Personally identifiable information may be linked to IP addresses to protect the security or integrity of the site.
Links to Other Sites
This site may contain links to other websites on the Internet. The information practices of those websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy or any other policies or terms applicable to this site. You should read the terms and policies of those other websites before supplying information to that site or otherwise using such site.
Children
This site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. SchoolSpring does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.
Additional Information about Privacy
If you have any concerns or questions about privacy on this site, please email us. You may also click on the "Contact Us" link at the bottom of each page.
Feedback
×Close
Tell us what you think!
